Md Khalilur Rahman

WordPrss Developer

- +8801834940597
- https://developerkhalil.com
- @ khalilsarafat676@gmail,com
- Pagura, Rajshahi, Bangladesh



SUMMARY

A highly skilled and proficient WordPress developer with over two years of professional experience in all aspects of WordPress website creation, including design, plug-ins, and implementation. Results-driven individual contributor with a successful track record in exceeding expectations for web development initiatives.

EXPERIENCE

Wordpress Developer

Freelancer.com

03/2021 - Ongoing Location

Crist is a web design agency specializing in rapid development of WordPress websites for small companies.

- Designed 4-5 online stores using WooCommerce
- Worked 50% development/50% task management
- Fast Loading Websites with Pagespeed Score above 80%

WORDPRESS DEVELOPER

Upwork

07/2021 - Ongoing

♀ 854 Su Van Hanh Street, Ward 13, District 10, Ho Chi Minh City

Stracke is a software solutions consulting and development firm, wit h our production office located in district 10, Ho Chi Minh City.

- Optimized website loading time performance by 3 times faster
- Created user interfaces across CIM applications using ExtJs 6 components like grid, tree etc
- Developed several Websites with Boostrap FrameWork and WordPress, HTML5, Javascript, CSS3
- Designed and developed more than 140 client websites with WordPress

WordPress Developer (Freelancer)

Fiverr

11/2016 - 2021

Location

Fiverr Ltd is a global freelancing platform where businesses and independent professionals connect and collaborate remotely.

- Managed a team of 3 developers and designers
- Developed and Managed 20+ Websites (Including company website)

SKILLS

WordPress

Web Design

Web Development

WooCommerce

Php

Jquary

Javascript

Mysql

EDUCATION

MBA

National University, **Bangladesh**

3.54 / 4.0

2010 - 2012

BBA

National University, Bangladesh

2007 - 2010

TRAINING / COURSES

Advance WordPress

SoftTech-IT

Advance Digital Marketing & Shopify Dropshipping

Webcoder-IT

STRENGTHS

Online Comunication

Effective online communication, present compelling messages in a one-way setting in order to be successful



Prioritize my tasks and efficiently organize everything to achieve my goals